<Start> : <Begin> <Middle> <End>
<Begin> : A(n) <Body> <Found> .
<Middle> : <Police> <Investigate> .
<End> : <Criminal> <Caught> .
<Body> : <Adjective> <Body> | corpse | body | skeleton | head
<Adjective> : rotting | insect-covered | blood-soaked | charred | decomposing
<Found> : is <Discovered> | is <Discovered> by a <Person> | is <Discovered> in <Location> | is <Discovered> by a <Person> in <Location>
<Discovered> : discovered | found | stumbled across | unearthed | disinterred | spotted | recognized | identified
<Police> : the police | the CSIs | NCIS | LAPD | NYPD | Stockton PD | the FBI | the local cops | a private eye | Jack Bauer | the secret service | the authorities
<Investigate> : <InitiallySuspect> <Person> then <ProcessEvidence> | <Investigate> and <Investigate>
<Criminal> : The perpetrator | The culprit | The guilty <Person> | The serial killer
<Caught> : is apprehended | is caught | is arrested | is shot in a face-off with <Police> | is taken away in handcuffs | is forced to flee the country | is taken into custody by <Police>
<Person> : neighbor | family member | homeless person | boss | wife | husband | mailman | garbage collector | gym teacher
<InitiallySuspect> : initially suspect the victim's | find evidence pointing to the | have a theory that the perpetrator is the | think that the crime was committed by the victim's
<ProcessEvidence> : <ProcessEvidence> and <ProcessEvidence> | run DNA analysis on the skin under the victim's fingernails | use the mass spectrometer to identify trace materials found on the victim's clothing | analyze the victim's blood and discover a rare poison | use blood spatter analysis to re-create the crime | swab the suspect's clothes for gunpowder residue | lift fingerprints from the murder weapon and run them through the FBI's database
<Location> : a deserted alleyway | a dumpster | a new homeowner's backyard | a swimming pool | a hotel room | a strip joint | an abandoned house | a local park | a seedy bar | an attic | the White House